MARCO DOMINGUES

19 Alexandra Road, London NW8 0DP marcodomingues.md@gmail.com +44 07 840 399 131

https://marcodominguesmd.github.io/portfolio/

I am a well organized and motivated customer service specialist with 2 years' experience working in various office environments. I am passionate about technology and in the past two years I have learned web development on my own. I like to build applications and websites from scratch, to find solution for the problems that I encounter along the coding. My goal is to become a game developer and build applications for mobile platforms. Currently I am looking for a position to start as a front end developer.

EDUCATION

Sept 2013 - Aug 2014 Reception Appprenticeship (France) CFA Trajectoire Hospitality Subject

Sept 2006 - 2010

Rocha Peixoto (Portugal) High School Degree Sports Subject

SKILLS

- ✓ HTML
- CSS
- ✓ JavaScript
- ✓ SASS
- **VueJS**
- NodeJS
- Portuguese (Mother tongue)
- French (Fluent)
- English (Fluent)
- Spanish (Very good)
- Italian (Basic)
- Hungarian (Beginner)

INTERESTS

- <> Web Development
- Games
- Travel
- **⊕** Gym
- Movies

WORK EXPERIENCE

March 2018 - Present

Tour Operator

MIKITRAVEL LTD.

Deal with tours to Portugal, France and Benelux. Filter requests from sales team to the hotel. Monitor and chase the hotel's reply. Assist the tours during and after their travel. Monitor rates and payment of the hotels.

March 2016 - 2018

Reception Supervisor

NOVOTEL LONDON PADDINGTON

Support the team. Create a fantastic first impression with a warm personalized welcome. Control of the tasks developed by the team. Ensure the staff is fully informed of all relevant information.

Sept 2013 - Sept 2014

Receptionist Team Member

NOVOTEL CONVENTION ET WELLNESS CDG (PARIS)

Take care of guests from their arrival through to their departure. Contribute with administrative tasks such as no shows, loyalty points program, guest credit. Preparation of flight crew member's reservations and arrivals.

Sept 2014 - Nov 2015

Receptionist Apprenticeship

NOVOTEL PARIS VAUGIRARD (PARIS)

Process the arrivals and departures of the customers. Contribute with administrative tasks, such as guest credit and control of arrivals. Assist guest with any concierge request.